[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9565759897232056, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 173, 'end': 183}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.98508620262146, 'word': 'Western Region', 'start': 192, 'end': 206}]
[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6047314405441284, 'word': 'NE', 'start': 25, 'end': 27}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7476423382759094, 'word': 'KANGR', 'start': 30, 'end': 35}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.4495900273323059, 'word': 'S', 'start': 44, 'end': 45}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.5064066648483276, 'word': 'Delhi', 'start': 56, 'end': 61}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.631999671459198, 'word': 'Ash', 'start': 71, 'end': 74}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8329534530639648, 'word': 'KAKA HALWA', 'start': 156, 'end': 166}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.47860223054885864, 'word': 'MA', 'start': 242, 'end': 244}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.3726145327091217, 'word': '##RAS', 'start': 246, 'end': 249}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5685632228851318, 'word': '&', 'start': 436, 'end': 437}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5063080191612244, 'word': 'A', 'start': 471, 'end': 472}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.7429631948471069, 'word': 'English Comprehension', 'start': 522, 'end': 543}]
[{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.910702109336853, 'word': 'Mumbai Centre', 'start': 288, 'end': 301}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.3737087845802307, 'word': 'ME', 'start': 323, 'end': 325}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.4547134339809418, 'word': 'Western', 'start': 347, 'end': 354}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7481644749641418, 'word': 'Central', 'start': 356, 'end': 363}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8619804978370667, 'word': 'Railways', 'start': 384, 'end': 392}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.32552477717399597, 'word': 'Examination', 'start': 478, 'end': 489}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.6554160118103027, 'word': 'OR', 'start': 942, 'end': 944}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.7978399395942688, 'word': 'Blue', 'start': 376, 'end': 380}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9979585409164429, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 804, 'end': 814}]
[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9991018772125244, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 59, 'end': 69}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9915077090263367, 'word': 'Exam Labs', 'start': 338, 'end': 347}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.7677240967750549, 'word': 'C', 'start': 532, 'end': 533}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9423587322235107, 'word': 'DE', 'start': 666, 'end': 668}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5790642499923706, 'word': 'Certificate', 'start': 348, 'end': 359}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.6451785564422607, 'word': 'Left T', 'start': 162, 'end': 168}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.7426595687866211, 'word': '##b I', 'start': 171, 'end': 174}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.46813350915908813, 'word': 'L', 'start': 185, 'end': 186}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9988929629325867, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 261, 'end': 271}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9989287257194519, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 909, 'end': 919}]
[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7543389797210693, 'word': 'Regional office', 'start': 759, 'end': 774}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9887908697128296, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 775, 'end': 785}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.6464520692825317, 'word': 'Computer Based', 'start': 976, 'end': 990}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.49780184030532837, 'word': 'Ex', 'start': 991, 'end': 993}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9613621830940247, 'word': 'Practice Test', 'start': 21, 'end': 34}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9986379742622375, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 69, 'end': 79}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8532809615135193, 'word': 'Regional Offices', 'start': 88, 'end': 104}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9345002174377441, 'word': 'Exam', 'start': 145, 'end': 149}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9660796523094177, 'word': 'Hindi', 'start': 172, 'end': 177}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9904119372367859, 'word': 'English', 'start': 178, 'end': 185}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9984754920005798, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 225, 'end': 235}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9171057343482971, 'word': 'Regional Offices', 'start': 240, 'end': 256}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8355382084846497, 'word': 'Regional Office', 'start': 412, 'end': 427}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9987483024597168, 'word': 'Commission', 'start': 436, 'end': 446}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5423647165298462, 'word': 'Certificate', 'start': 545, 'end': 556}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5430569052696228, 'word': 'Screen', 'start': 878, 'end': 884}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5784128904342651, 'word': 'Ce', 'start': 996, 'end': 998}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5782956480979919, 'word': 'Ex', 'start': 217, 'end': 219}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5551502704620361, 'word': 'Paper', 'start': 519, 'end': 524}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9991214871406555, 'word': 'English', 'start': 721, 'end': 728}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9986230134963989, 'word': 'Hindi', 'start': 733, 'end': 738}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9398490786552429, 'word': 'Question', 'start': 177, 'end': 185}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.7415715456008911, 'word': 'Previous Question', 'start': 189, 'end': 206}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.8827145099639893, 'word': 'Question', 'start': 817, 'end': 825}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5824084877967834, 'word': 'Question', 'start': 838, 'end': 846}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.563539981842041, 'word': '##mark', 'start': 345, 'end': 349}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.49067434668540955, 'word': 'De', 'start': 405, 'end': 407}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6080111861228943, 'word': 'Green Box', 'start': 558, 'end': 567}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.4590664505958557, 'word': 'Amber Box', 'start': 627, 'end': 636}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5342649221420288, 'word': 'Violet Box', 'start': 693, 'end': 703}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.40333327651023865, 'word': 'B', 'start': 741, 'end': 742}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.4004184901714325, 'word': 'Box', 'start': 747, 'end': 750}]
[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.7690677046775818, 'word': 'Pre', 'start': 18, 'end': 21}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.8216139674186707, 'word': 'Sub', 'start': 26, 'end': 29}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.5444090962409973, 'word': 'N', 'start': 43, 'end': 44}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.7045340538024902, 'word': 'C', 'start': 340, 'end': 341}]PER